(Mrs Cooper:)from one of his friends.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)But I wasn't.
'Cause I didn't
have any friends.
(laughs):
No.
(Mrs Cooper:)It turns out that this
little scallywag was trying
(Mrs Cooper:)to use my Visa card
to buy uranium
(Mrs Cooper:)from an African warlord
in the country of Chad!
(Dr Hofstadter:)Sounds like Sheldon
was a handful.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, he was a handful.
(Sheldon:)I was a handful.
(Leonard:)You still are.
(Leonard:)Uh, Mom, hey,
tell Mary the story
(Leonard:)about how I made
a Van de Graaff generator
(Leonard:)out of our vacuum cleaner.
(Dr Hofstadter:)All right.
(Dr Hofstadter:)He broke the
vacuum cleaner.
(video game sound effects
playing)
(Howard:)I mean, for a while,
everything was vampires.
(Howard:)Now it's all zombies.
(Howard:)I wonder what the next
monster fad will be.
(Raj:)We haven't had a good
invisible man in a while.